http://www.showvisiontalent.com/privacy-policy/

Bands Comedians Entertainers Musicians Tributes
Privacy Policy
ShowVision Talent respects that privacy is an important concern for our users. By submitting personal data, a visitor to our website is agreeing to ShowVision Talent’s use of such data as described in this privacy Policy.
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.showvisiontalent.com and applies only to information collected by this website. We only collect the information you provide to us through e-mail or other direct contact. Your information—name, address, phone number, etc.—will not be released to third parties, in Canada or elsewhere.
ShowVision Talent is the owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell or lease this information to anyone. We may use the information you sent to us to respond to you, to deliver services that we offer, and to create sales opportunities. You always have the option to opt out.
We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. We may contact you by e-mail in the future to tell you about specials, new services or products. We will not contact you if you ask us not to, and you can stop any future contacts from us at any time.
We may contact you in the future about changes to our Privacy Policy. We take care in protecting the information you submit through the website.
You can contact us anytime to update your information, provide feedback about the ways in which your data is being used, and ask us to delete any data we have relevant to you.
Your personal information is stored only in the province of Ontario, Canada. Should you decide that you would no longer like to be contacted by ShowVision Talent, notify us and we will remove you from our contact list.
We will access your information when we need to for billing and for customer service purposes.
The computers in which we store personal information are in a secure environment. Payments are not made through this website. We accept credit card payments through PayPal Canada, Interac e-transfer and cheque.
When you submit your registration information to us through our website forms, you are required to submit certain data to us such as name, e-mail and telephone.
If you apply for talent representational through the ShowVision Talent, your personal contact information will not be posted on our website, only information related to your entertainment/talent skills and abilities will be posted on our site, where the public will be able to view the information. We may disclose and communicate your personal information if required to do so by law including by an order of any court.
We may use the contact information that you provide in the online registration forms to contact you by telephone or e-mail, regarding opportunities, updates on the site, or for marketing purposes.		ShowVision Talent respects that privacy is an important concern for our users. By submitting personal data, a visitor to our website is agreeing to ShowVision Talent’s use of such data as described in this privacy Policy.
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.showvisiontalent.com and applies only to information collected by this website. We only collect the information you provide to us through e-mail or other direct contact. Your information—name, address, phone number, etc.—will not be released to third parties, in Canada or elsewhere.
ShowVision Talent is the owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell or lease this information to anyone. We may use the information you sent to us to respond to you, to deliver services that we offer, and to create sales opportunities. You always have the option to opt out.
We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request. We may contact you by e-mail in the future to tell you about specials, new services or products. We will not contact you if you ask us not to, and you can stop any future contacts from us at any time.
We may contact you in the future about changes to our Privacy Policy. We take care in protecting the information you submit through the website.
You can contact us anytime to update your information, provide feedback about the ways in which your data is being used, and ask us to delete any data we have relevant to you.
Your personal information is stored only in the province of Ontario, Canada. Should you decide that you would no longer like to be contacted by ShowVision Talent, notify us and we will remove you from our contact list.
We will access your information when we need to for billing and for customer service purposes.
The computers in which we store personal information are in a secure environment. Payments are not made through this website. We accept credit card payments through PayPal Canada, Interac e-transfer and cheque.
When you submit your registration information to us through our website forms, you are required to submit certain data to us such as name, e-mail and telephone.
If you apply for talent representational through the ShowVision Talent, your personal contact information will not be posted on our website, only information related to your entertainment/talent skills and abilities will be posted on our site, where the public will be able to view the information. We may disclose and communicate your personal information if required to do so by law including by an order of any court.
We may use the contact information that you provide in the online registration forms to contact you by telephone or e-mail, regarding opportunities, updates on the site, or for marketing purposes.
